<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andy&#39;s Blog</title>
    <description>Andy&#39;s Viget Internship Blog</description>
    <link>http://andycandrea.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://andycandrea.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog! This is where I’ll be chronicling my summer as a Rails Dev intern at Viget’s Durham office. I’ll be keeping track of my progress on each of the projects that I work on, the technologies that I’m learning and any interesting resources or bugs I come across. Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/welcome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/welcome.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 2 - The Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though I got started making this blog yesterday, I got the chance to devote a lot more time to it today. I had managed to get the basic functionality done yesterday afternoon in between orientation meetings, so I started off the day working on the aesthetic. After tinkering with the layout and color scheme for a few hours, I decided to add a comment feature, so I spent some time looking at &lt;a href=&quot;http://disqus.com/&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.intensedebate.com/&quot;&gt;IntenseDebate&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/phusion/juvia&quot;&gt;Juvia&lt;/a&gt;. While I really appreciated that Juvia was open source, I was turned off by the fact that it doesn’t seem well supported—several of the most recent commit messages reference starting to upgrade for Rails 3.2 rather than the current 4.1. As a result, I ended up going for Disqus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I decided on Disqus, I considered using &lt;a href=&quot;http://octopress.org/&quot;&gt;Octopress&lt;/a&gt;, a Jekyll framework, to tie it into what I’d already written. After tinkering around with it for a while, though, I ended up deciding against it; it didn’t seem like it would really add much of anything to my blog (at least at the moment) aside from a little extra bloat. Plus, it turned out that setting up Disqus with Jekyll is &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/472138-jekyll-installation-instructions&quot;&gt;incredibly easy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish off the day, I added a link to an RSS feed of my blog’s five most recent posts. Since I’m no XML pro, and I’ve never used RSS—as either a developer or even as a reader—I ended up using the directions found &lt;a href=&quot;http://joelglovier.com/writing/rss-for-jekyll/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; by Joel Glovier and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/snaptortoise/jekyll-rss-feeds&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; by snaptortoise, making the requisite edit to show the posts from the last week (in order words, the last five posts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, I may work on the “improve searchability” task that Patrick put up on Basecamp and/or work on making my layout a little more mobile-friendly–the layout works on mobile/small browser windows thanks to Bootstrap, but it could still use some tinkering. Regardless of what I do with the blog, I’d definitely like to dive into some Rails, so I’ll probably start on some of the basics for the Hacker News clone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/day-2-the-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/day-2-the-blog.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My first day was mostly spent setting up my machine, which consisted of installing the different technologies I’ll be using over the course of the summer–Ruby, Rails, etc–and getting reacquainted with OSX. I also got to learn more about Viget and started constructing this blog, which required getting myself familiar with Jekyll. In addition to Jekyll, I also used Bootstrap for the nav bar and basic layout help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/day-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://andycandrea.github.io//2014/06/10/day-1.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
